Tufts Women Employees' Newsletters UP193
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Women Employees' Newsletters
1973 -- 1976
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Women Employees
UP193
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes two newsletters published by women's organizations at Tufts. Affiliation of Women for Active and Relevant Education (Aware) was for women administrators and professors, while Tufts Women Employees (TWE) was for other women employees.
Biographical / Historical
In February 1974, a group of women employees at Tufts formed to "discuss common concerns, improve the lines of communication, and foster a spirit of cooperation and support among faculty, administrative and secretarial women on the Medford campus."
- Tufts Womens Employees' Newsletters, 1973 -- 1976; UP193.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes two newsletters published by women's organizations at Tufts. Affiliation of Women for Active and Relevant Education (Aware) was for women administrators and professors, while Tufts Women Employees (TWE) was for other women employees.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by newsletter and then chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Aware, 1973 September; UP193.001.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.44 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Aware, 1973 October-November; UP193.001.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.57 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Aware, 1973 December; UP193.001.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.67 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 February 21; UP193.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 February 28; UP193.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 March 08; UP193.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 March 14; UP193.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 May 08; UP193.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 September; UP193.001.001.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.48 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 October; UP193.001.001.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.63 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1974 November; UP193.001.001.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.19 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1975 January; UP193.001.001.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.82 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1975 February; UP193.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1975 July; UP193.001.001.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.29 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1975 November; UP193.001.001.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.61 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1975 December - 1976 January; UP193.001.001.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.35 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 February; UP193.001.001.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.17 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 March; UP193.001.001.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.28 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 April; UP193.001.001.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.32 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 May; UP193.001.001.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.3 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 June; UP193.001.001.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.64 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 October; UP193.001.001.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.16 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 September; UP193.001.001.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.26 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 November; UP193.001.001.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.85 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Women Employees [TWE] Newsletter, 1976 December; UP193.001.001.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.93 Megabytes (Box 1)